Franklin-Bache Papers 1707-1799 Mss.B.F85.ba
American Philosophical Society
- Franklin-Bache Papers, 1707-1799; B F85.ba; 4 lin. feet
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 March 13; Lee, Arthur, 1740-1792
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 March 16; Lee, Arthur, 1740-1792
  - to Benjamin Franklin, Silas Deane and Lee, 1778 March 20; Rocquette, J. etc.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1778] March 26; Condorcet, Jean-Antoine-Nicolas de, marquis de, 1743-1794
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 April 9; Mengaud
  - to Van Berckel, 1778 April 10; United States. Commissioners
  - to Dumas, 1778 April 10; United States. Commissioners
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 April 23; de Pavin, Col.
  - Receipted bill for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling for two quarters, 1778 April 23; Le Coeur, M.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 April 25; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 April 27; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 May 27; Holtzman
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 May 29; St. Juste
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 May 30; Welffen, Baron de
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 June 1; Buffot de Millery, M.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 June 18; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - Personal account with Ferdinand Grand, 1778 June 30-1789 April 8; Franklin, Benjamin (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 July 14; Bache, Richard
  - Inventory of Silas Deane's home furnishings, 1778 July 16; Deane, Silas, 1737-1789
  - Receipt for 750,000 livres, 1778 August 3
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 August 15; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 Sept. 4; Williams, D.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [ca. 1778] Sept; Bradford, John, Jr.
  - to Louis XVI, Franklin's letter of credence, 1778 Oct. 21; United States. Continental Congress. (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 Oct. 24; Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 Oct. 24; Partridge, Elizabeth
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 Oct. 26; United States. Continental Congress. (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 Oct. 26; United States. Continental Congress. (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1778 Oct. 28; United States. Committee for Foreign Affairs
  - Bill of exchange, 1778 Nov. 25
  - Bill of exchange, 1778 Nov. 30
  - Bill of exchange, 1778 Nov. 30
  - Bill of exchange, 1778 Dec. 1
  - Bill of exchange, 1778 Dec. 1
  - Detail de l'assassinat premedite.., [ca. 1778?]; Lotbinière, Michel-Alain Chartier de
  - [1778?], Melmoth, Courtney
  - 1779 Jan. 1-Febraury 1, Journals; United States. Continental Congress. (Oversize X)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Jan. 2; Partridge, Elizabeth
    [see folder for 1778 Oct. 24]
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Jan. 4; Mecom, Jane
  - to Franklin, Lee and Adams, 1779 Jan. 5; Massachusetts
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Jan. 16; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Feb. 14; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Feb. 16; Bache, Richard
  - Franklin's memo of shares and coupons, 1779 Feb. 19-1784 July 27
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Feb. 27; Mecom, Jane
    [see folder for 1779 Feb. 14]
  - Bill of exchange, 1779 March 18
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 March 27; Washington, George
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 April 7; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 April 7; Shipley, Anna M.
  - Receipted bill from Lecoeur for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling for two quarters, 1779 April 15
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 May 1; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 May 12; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - to Anna M. Shipley, 1779 May 25; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Congress report of Committee on Mr. de Francey's memorial, 1779 June 5
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 June 6; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - Report, 1779 June 18; United States. Congress. Committee on the Treasury
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 June [18]; Jay, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 June 23; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 July 27; Mecom, Jane
  - to W. J. Franklin, 1779 August 8; Grand, H.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 August 12; Peters, W.
  - Receipt from M. Grand, 1779 Sept. 3
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Sept. 12; Mecom, Jane
  - Bill of exchange, 1779 Sept. 15
  - Bill of exchange, 1779 Sept. 15
  - Bill of exchange, 1779 Sept. 15
  - Bill of exchange, 1779 Sept. 15
  - Bill of exchange, 1779 Sept. 15 [?]
  - Promissory note, no. 2, 1779 Sept. 16
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Sept. 18; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Sept. 25; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Oct. 1; Shipley, Anna M.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Oct. 2; Bache, Sarah
  - Promissory note, no. 3, 1779 Oct. 4
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Oct. 17; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Oct. 18; Bache, Richard
  - Order granting permission for a cartel to John Jackson, et al, 1779 Oct. 25; Massachusetts. Council
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Nov. 2; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Nov. 2; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Nov. 8; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Nov. 14; Bache, Sarah
  - Agreement with items laid down Massachusetts Council in permitting them to depart for England, 1779 Nov. 20; Jackson, John et al
  - to Henry Mitchell, [1779 Nov. 20]; Massachusetts. Council
  - to Henry Mitchell, 1779 Nov. 20; Massachusetts. Council
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1779] Nov.; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1779 Dec. 31; Strahan, William
  - Receipted bill from G. L. Marignac for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling, etc., from Sept. 5-Oct. 5, 1779
  - Tableau general des Postes pour l'année 1779 (Oversize X)
  - to Jonathan Williams, Jr, 1780 Jan. 9; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Jan. 10; Cramer, Catherine de Wesselow
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Jan. 15; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to [William Strahan], 1780 Jan. 24; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Sir Grey Cooper, and Thomas Symons to Sir Grey Cooper, 1780 Jan. 28; Mitchell, Henry (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1780?] Jan. 31; Allaire, P.
  - List of bills drawn on le Ray de Chaumont for soldiers' clothing, 1780 Feb. 1-August 3; Williams, Jonathan Jr. (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Feb. 3; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Feb. 4; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Feb. 9; Houston, W. C.
  - to J. Williams, Jr, 1780 Feb. 14; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to the Lords of the Admiralty, 1780 Feb. 15; Mitchell, Henry (Oversize 1)
  - to Sir Phillip Stephens, 1780 Feb. 15; Symons, Thomas
  - to Joshua Johnson, 1780 Feb. 22; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Williams, Jonathan Jr, 1780 Feb. 23; Franklin, Benjamin
    [see folder for 1780 Feb. 22]
  - Promissory note, no. 5, 1780 Feb. 29
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1780 Feb. ?]; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - Bill of exchange, 1780 March 1
  - Congressional resolutions, 1780 March 18, 20, 21 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 March 27; Mecom, Jane (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 March 28; Peters, Richard, 1743-1828
  - Bill of exchange, 1780 March 29
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 March 29; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 March 29; Banks, Joseph
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 2, 5; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 21; Matlack, Timothy
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 22; Hopkinson, Francis
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 25; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 28; Peters, Richard, 1743-1828
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 28; Peters, Richard, 1743-1828
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 28; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 29; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 April 29; Rittenhouse, David, 1732-1796
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 May 2; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 May 2; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 May 2; Webster, P.
  - Bill of exchange, 1780 May 15
  - Bill of exchange, 1780 May 17
  - Congressional resolutions, 1780 May 19, August 9, 15, 23, 30 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 May 26; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - Bill of exchange, 1780 June 6
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 June 9; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to J. Williams, Jr, 1780 June 17; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 June 23; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 June 26; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - Table of payment of... interest.., 1780 June 28 (Oversize Floor D)
  - Inventory of founts cast before July, 1780 and after July 22, 1780, 1780 ante-July; Passy press.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 July 2; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 July 14; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - By Hemery [?] Account of founts made at Passy, 1780 July 22
  - London Courant, 1780 July 26 (Oversize 1)
  - to J. Williams, Jr, 1780 July 29; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Sept. 9; Marignac, Gabriel L.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Sept. 10; Bache, Richard
  - Resolution, 1780 Oct. 2; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1780 Oct. 5; United States. Congress (Oversize Floor D)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Oct. 9; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Oct. 21; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Oct. 25; Morris, Robert
  - to Williams, Jonathan Jr, 1780 Oct. 28; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Oct. 30; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Nov. 5; Gale, B.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Nov. 7; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Nov. 23; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Samuel Huntington? Bills of exchange, 1780 Nov. 23; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Proposed form of draft on Congress, 1780 Nov. 24; Williams, Jonathan.
  - Memo of conversation with Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Nov. 26; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Mr. Grand, 1780 Dec. 4; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 6 [?]; Receipt from Grand
  - to S. Cooper, 1780 Dec. 9; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 12; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 16; Peters, Richard, 1743-1828
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 18; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 19; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 20; Bache, Richard
  - List of bills drawn on Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 20; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 20; Washington, George
  - Congressional order, 1780 Dec. 21
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 21; Priestley, Joseph Rayner
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 22
  - to John Laurens, 1780 Dec. 23; Continental Congress (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 24; Mecom, Jane (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 26; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 27; Continental Congress (Oversize 1)
  - to Jonathan Williams, Jr, 1780 Dec. 27; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 28; Greene, Catherine Ray
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 29; Peters, Richard, 1743-1828
  - Joseph Bogey Receipted bill, 1780 Dec. 30
  - Receipted bill, Coimet, 1780 Dec. 30
  - Receipted bill. Francois, 1780 Dec. 30
  - Receipted bill. Arbelot, 1780 Dec. 31
  - Receipted bill. Arbelot, 1780 Dec. 31
  - Receipt-coimet, 1780 Dec. 31
  - Receipted bill. Cruchot, 1780 Dec. 31
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1780 Dec. 31; Rittenhouse, David, 1732-1796
  - to Le Ray de Chaumont, [1780 Dec.]; Rayneval, Joseph Gérard de
  - for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling, etc. from Oct. 5, 1779-Jan. 5, 1780, Marignac, Gabriel L.
  - for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling, etc. from Jan. 5-May 5, 1780, Marignac, Gabriel L.
  - for Benjamin Franklin Bache's schooling, etc. from May 5, 1780-Sept. 5, 1780, Marignac, Gabriel L.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [ca. 1780]; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - Contract re Franklin's Account, [ca. 1780]; Le Ray de Chaumont and Williams, Jonathan.
  - Memo of accounts, [ca. 1780]
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 1; Greene, Catherine Ray
  - Receipt -- Franklin, 1781 Jan. 1
  - Receipt -- Journal de Paris, 1781 Jan. 3
  - Receipt -- Magars, 1781 Jan. 4
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 6; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - Receipted bill -- Francois, 1781 Jan. 7
  - Receipted bill -- Francois, 1781 Jan. 7
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 7; Lunier, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 8; Mouret, J.
  - to Jonathan Williams, 1781 Jan. 12; Adams, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 15; Washington, George
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 20; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 23; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - Account of contents of 34 boxes of printing letters, etc. cast at Passy, 1781 Jan. 27
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 30; J. and W. Russell
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Jan. 31; Greene, W. and Catharine
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Feb. 3; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Feb. 5; Marignac, Gabriel L.
    [see folder for 1780 Sept. 9]
  - to Grand, 1781 Feb. 10; Franklin, Benjamin
    [see folder for 1780 september 9]
  - Promissory note, no. 10, 1781 Feb. 15
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 March 1; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 March 3; Mecom, Jane (Oversize 1)
  - to the Baron de la Courtelle, 1781 March 24; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 March 28; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 April 8; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Gabriel Marignac, 1781 April 16; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1781 April 16; Franklin, Benjamin
    [see folder for 1781 April 16, Benjamin Franklin to Gabriel L. Marignac.]
  - to S. Huntington, 1781 May 3; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 7; Carroll, C.
  - to S. Cooper, 1781 May 15; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Promissory note, no. 11, 1781 May 15
  - to F. Lewis, 1781 May 16; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 16; Laurens, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 16; Laurens, John
  - to John Laurens?, 1781 May 16
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 22; Laurens, John (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 28; Laurens, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 28; Laurens, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 29; Laurens, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 May 30; Laurens, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 6; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 8; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 12; Harris, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 13; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 15; Witherspoon, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 18; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 20; D. of St. T. Jenifer
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 22; Bache, Richard
  - Resolutions, 1781 June 25; Pennsylvania. General Assembly
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 June 28
  - to la Luzerne, 1781 July 2; Morris, Robert
  - Promissory note, 1781 July 2
    [see folder for 1778 August 3]
  - to Robert Morris, 1781 July 3; Barbé-Marbois, Francois, marquis de, 1745-1837
  - to Francois Barbé-Marbois, 1781 July 4; Morris, Robert
  - Receipted bill-Coimet, 1781 July 4
  - to Governors of respective states, 1781 July 6; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 July 9; Jordan, D.
  - Receipted bill-Delbos, 1781 July 9
  - Receipted bill-Bligny, 1781 July 12
  - Receipted bill-Joseph Bogey, 1781 July 14
  - Campo de Arbe-Receipt, 1781 July 14
  - Wrapper for accounts, 1781 July 14-1782 Feb. 12
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 July 15; Logan, G.
  - Receipted bill-Arbelot, 1781 July 16
  - to governors of respective states, 1781 July 16; Morris, Robert
  - Receipted bill-Francois, 1781 July 16
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 July 17; Hopkinson, F.
  - Receipt, 1781 July 18; Chaumont, Le Ray de
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 July 18; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - Promissory note, no. 15, 1781 July 18
  - Promissory note, no. 15, 1781 July 18
  - to Governors of the respective states, 1781 July 25; Morris, Robert
  - to Governors of respective states, 1781 July 27; Morris, Robert
  - Receipted bill-Francois Garnier, 1781 July 30
  - to Chev. de la Luzerne, 1781 August 2; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 August 2; Trumbull, J.
  - to Robert Morris, 1781 August 3; de la Luzerne, Chev.
  - to Thomas McKean, 1781 August 6; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 August 8; Jones, Capt. John Paul (Oversize 1)
  - to Epidorge, 1781 August 12; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Promissory note, no. 12, 1781 August 15
  - Receipted bill-Brunel, 1781 August 18
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 August 20; Gill, J. M.
  - to Thomas McKean, 1781 August 28; Morris, Robert
  - Receipt- Courier de l' Europe, 1781 August 29
  - Receipt, 1781 August 29
  - Receipt-Mme. de St. Louis, 1781 Sept. 1
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Septermber 5; D. of St. T. Jenifer
  - Receipted bill-Mme. de St. Louis, 1781 Sept. 10
  - Report of Committee on letter from William Lee, 1781 Sept. 12; United States. Continental Congress.
  - Receipt-Fouchet, 1781 Sept. 14
  - Receipted bill-Cabaret, 1781 Sept. 15 (Oversize 1)
  - to John Hancock, 1781 Sept. 15; Morris, Robert
  - Receipted bill-Bernard, 1781 Sept. 15
  - Receipted bill-Deane, 1781 Sept. 16
  - Receipt-Zully[?], 1781 Sept. 16
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Sept. 17; Jones, W.
  - Receipt-Campo-de-Arbe, 1781 Sept. 17
  - Receipt-Carpentier, 1781 Sept. 18
  - Receipt-Nivert, 1781 Sept. 20
  - to Robert Morris, [1781] Sept. 24; La Luzerne, Chevalier de
  - to Chev. de la Luzerne, 1781 Sept. 25; Morris, Robert
  - to Robert Morris, 1781 Sept. 26; La Luzerne, Chevalier de
  - to ----, 1781 Sept. 28; Morris, Robert
  - Receipt, 1781 Sept. 30
  - Promissory note, no. 16, 1781 Oct. 1
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 3; Hopkinson, Francis
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 4; Corny, Dominique-Louis Ethis de
  - Receipt Mme. de St. Louis, 1781 Oct. 6
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 7; Greene, Catherine Ray
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 8; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - Receipted bill-Aury, 1781 Oct. 11
  - to Loan Officers of 13 U.S, 1781 Oct. 13; Morris, Robert
  - Receipted bill-Benard, 1781 Oct. 14
  - Receipt-Campo-de-Arbe, 1781 Oct. 14
  - to Thomas Nelson, 1781 Oct. 16; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 18; Johnson, M.
  - to Governors of the respective states, 1781 Oct. 19; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 20; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - to John Trumbull, 1781 Oct. 21; Deane, Silas, 1737-1789
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 23; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 26; Cushing, T.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 27; Cooper, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 27; Cooper, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 28; Partridge, E.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Oct. 29; Mecom, Jane
  - Resolution, 1781 Oct. 30; United States. Congress
  - Promissory note, no. 17, 1781 Oct. 30
  - Receipted bills-Arbelot, 1781 Oct. 30
  - Receipted bill-Benard, 1781 Oct. 30
  - Receipt-Franks, 1781 Nov. 2
  - Congressional Resolutions, 1781 Nov. 2
  - to the Chev. de la Luzerne, 1781 Nov. 3; Morris, Robert
  - to Robert Morris, 1781 Nov. 4; de la Luzerne, Chev.
  - to Thomas McKean, 1781 Nov. 5; Morris, Robert
  - to la Luzerne, 1781 Nov. 6; Morris, Robert
  - Receipt-Subscription for Mercure de France, 1781 Nov. 11
  - Congressional Resolutions, 1781 Nov. 12
    [See folder for 1781 Nov. 2]
  - Receipted bill-Cabaret, 1781 Nov. 12 (Oversize 1)
  - Promissory note, no. 13, 1781 Nov. 15
  - to Governors of respective states, 1781 Nov. 17; Morris, Robert
  - Receipt-Campo-de-Arbe, 1781 Nov. 17
  - Receipted bill-Cressonnier, 1781 Nov. 17
  - Receipted bill-Chocarne, 1781 Nov. 18
  - Receipted bill-Cressonnier, 1781 Nov. 18
  - to the Chevalier de la Luzerne, 1781 Nov. 22; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Nov. 24; Bache, Richard
  - to Robert Morris, 1781 Nov. 24; de la Luzerne, Chev.
  - Board of War. Invoices of articles..., 1781 Nov. 25
  - Receipt- Charles Ciceri, 1781 Nov. 25
  - Receipt- Cressonnier, 1781 Nov. 25
  - to Robert Morris, 1781 Nov. 26; de la Luzerne, Chevalier
  - to chevalier de la Luzerne, 1781 Nov. 26; Morris, Robert
  - Resolution, 1781 Nov. 27; United States. Congress (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Nov. 27; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Nov. 30; Hopkinson, Francis
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Nov. 30; Hopkinson, Francis
  - 1781 Dec. 2, Poor woman seeking assistance.
  - Resolution, 1781 Dec. 3; [see folder for 1781 Nov. 27]; United States. Congress (Oversize 1)
  - Receipt-Mazars, 1781 Dec. 3
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Dec. 6; Partridge, E.
  - Receipted bill-Arbelot, 1781 Dec. 9
  - Receipted bill-Benard, 1781 Dec. 9
  - Receipted bill-Joseph Bogey, 1781 Dec. 9
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Dec. 10; Priestley, Joseph Rayner
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Dec. 13; Jones, Capt. John Paul
  - Receipted bill-Roger, 1781 Dec. 14
  - to William Temple Franklin, 1781 Dec. 15; Alexander, William
  - to the Governors of North Carolina, South Carolina and Georgia, 1781 Dec. 19; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Dec. 20; Curson and Gouverneur
  - Receipted bill-Barrois, Sr, 1781 Dec. 21
  - Receipted bill-Pissot, 1781 Dec. 21
  - Receipted bill-Coimet, 1781 Dec. 22
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1781 Dec. 28; Hillegas, M.
  - Receipted bill-Apothecary, 1781 Dec. 28
  - Receipt- Journal de Paris., 1781 Dec. 29
  - Receipted bill-Bery, 1781 Dec. 29
  - Receipted bill ----, 1781 Dec. 29
  - Delafall [?]-Receipt, 1781 Dec. 31
  - Memo of accounts, 1781 Dec. 31; Franklin, William Temple
  - ----- Receipt, 1782 [i.e. 1781?] Dec. 31
  - [1781] Sunday, Laurens, John
  - [1781] Sunday morning, Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809
  - [1781?] Wednesday AM, La Rochefoucauld, Louis Alexandre, duc de
  - Jackson, W.
  - [1781], Laurens, John
  - [1781], Paine, Thomas, 1737-1809
  - to Governors of states, 1782 Jan. 3; Morris, Robert
  - to Governors of respective states, 1782 Jan. 3; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Jan. 3; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1782 Jan. 7; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Jan. 7; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - Receipt-Campo-de-Arbe, 1782 Jan. 8
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Jan. 9; Bache, Richard
  - Receipted bill-Chocarne, 1782 Jan. 9
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Jan. 9; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - Receipted bill-Bery, 1782 Jan. 12
  - Receipt-Gondal, 1782 Jan. 16
  - Receipt, 1782 Jan. 16
  - to W. T. Franklin, 1782 Jan. 16; Vaughan, J.
  - Memo by W. T. Franklin, 1782 Jan. 23
  - to W. T. Franklin, 1782 Jan. 25; Hoops, A.
  - Receipt-Lucien, 1782 Jan. 28
  - Receipted bill-Angenend, 1782 Jan. 29
  - Receipted bill-Benard, 1782 Feb. 5
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Feb. 5; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - Resolution, 1782 Feb. 8; United States. Congress
  - Promissory note, no.19, 1782 Feb. 8
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Feb. 9; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Feb. 9; de Marignac, G. L. G.
  - to Benjamin Franklin. [Lafayette?], 1782 Feb. 12; Wallace, Johnson and Muir
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 1; Jay, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 5; Jones, W.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 8; Pringuet
  - Promissory note, no. 20, 1782 March 12
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 20; Bondfield, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 23; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 23; Bourse, Joseph
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 24; Bondfield, J.
  - Drawing of Passy garden [?], 1782 March 27; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 March 29; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 11; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 13; Bondfield, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 13; Hopkins, D.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 14; Martin, C.B. Jr. (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 15; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 22; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 25; Barclay, Thomas